shoppingvouchers.co.uk 2013-04-05

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy for Ommven Ltd t/a ShoppingVouchers.co.uk.

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Ommven Limited, a company incorporated in England & Wales with company number 07369969 and having its registered office at 1st Floor, Vectra House, 36 Paradise Road, Richmond, TW9 1SE ("we", "us", "our"). Our website is www.shoppingvouchers.co.uk (the "Site"). By submitting personal data manually or in electronic form to us in connection with the Site you give your consent that all personal data that you submit will be processed by us in the manner and for the purposes described below. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. If you have any questions at all about this policy or the Site, or about how we use and process your personal information, please do not hesitate to contact us by e-mail at contact@shoppingvouchers.co.uk or, alternatively, in writing to www.shoppingvouchers.co.uk c/o Ommven Limited, New Lodge, Drift Road, Windsor, SL4 4RR 

### Information Collection and Use

We are fully committed to protecting the privacy of the users of our Site. We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from those disclosed in this statement.

We collect information from you at several different points on the Site.

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the Site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the Site will constitute your agreement to any such changes.

When you submit personal information in connection with making a payment via the Site, such personal information is encrypted and protected with encryption software which lets your browser automatically encrypt data before you send it to us. While on a secure page the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

The data we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination located out side of the European Economic Area ("EEA"). By providing information to this Site you expressly consent to such information being transferred or stored outside of the EEA.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and although we take all reasonable steps to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of it. Any transmission of personal data to the Site is at your own risk.

### Registration

In order to use the Site you may wish to register, you must first complete the registration form and all details required in it. During registration you are required to give your contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about those services on the Site in which you have expressed an interest. It is optional for you to provide other demographic information, but this is encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience of the Site.

### Disclosures of your Information

We may disclose your information to third parties in the following circumstances, where:-

  * (i) you consent to such disclosure;
  * (ii) we are legally required to do so by regulatory or law enforcement authorities;
  * (iii) we, in good faith, believe it necessary to protect the personal safety of users or the public;
  * (iv) we (in whole or in part) merge with, or are acquired by, another business. If this happens, we may share any information or data that relates to you with any party who acquires all or part of the business; and/or
  * (v) we are the subject of insolvency proceedings, whereby information may be disposed of in such a way as required by the courts.

We also reserve the right to disclose the information collected about you to our professional advisors.

### Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners, clients and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When you sign up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

We may also use such aggregated information and statistics for monitoring the Site usage in order to help us develop the Site and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the Site. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on the Site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on the Site. If you reject the cookie, you may not be able to use every function of the Site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target your interests to enhance your experience of the Site. Some of our business partners use cookies on this Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the Site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Links

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by us on the Site.

### Direct Mailings

We occasionally send out newsletters, discount books or alerts to our members. We may also wish to provide you with information about special features of our Site or any other service or products we think may be of interest to you. This is an opt-in email option selected when you register to the Site. At any time you can alter your personal profile on the Site to disable any further emails.

From time to time the Site will request information from you via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postcode or age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of and satisfaction with this site.

### Email-A-Friend

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. This information is then discarded after the email is sent.

### Data Protection Act 1998

We make every effort to ensure that our practices, procedures and systems comply with the relevant data protection legislation and we are registered as a data controller for the purposes of the Act.

For more details about your rights under the Act, the rules we have to adhere to in collecting and storing your information, and how you can check your data records, please visit www.dataprotection.gov.uk.

You have a right to receive a copy of the information we hold about you by sending your request in writing to www.shoppingvouchers.co.uk c/o Ommven Limited, New Lodge, Drift Road, Windsor, SL4 4RR

### Updating/Removal of Personal Information

If any information regarding you requires to be corrected, updated or changed it is your responsibility to advise us of the required amendments.

If you inform us that you no longer desire our service, we shall correct, update or remove your personal data provided to us. Please note, an archive copy of any information provided to us may be retained by us for our records and for audit purposes.

### Contact

If you have any questions at all about this policy or the Site, or about how we use and process your personal information, please do not hesitate to contact us at us by e-mail at contact@shoppingvouchers.co.uk or, alternatively, in writing to www.shoppingvouchers.co.uk c/o Ommven Limited, 1st Floor, Vectra House, 36 Paradise Road, Richmond, TW9 1SE
